http://www.andritz.com/group-en/privacy-policy

Cookie Settings
ANDRITZ recognizes the importance of protecting the personal privacy of its customers, potential customers, employees, potential employees, investors, suppliers, consortium partners and website visitors. This data privacy declaration describes the information that may be collected by ANDRITZ legal entities, through our websites, through our locations and through your communications with us. It also provides information on your rights and the choices you can make regarding our use of your personal information and how we protect it.SCOPE AND TERMS USEDWhile this website may contain links to other websites, this data privacy declaration applies to the andritz.com website operated by ANDRITZ AG. Unless otherwise indicated, all references to “ANDRITZ,” “we” or “our” in this data privacy declaration shall mean the ANDRITZ GROUP.Some of the sites may contain links to the websites of other ANDRITZ legal entities or to the websites of third parties. ANDRITZ is not responsible and has no liability for the privacy policies or practices of those websites. We recommend that you review the data privacy declaration of each website you visit.As used in this data privacy declaration, “personal information” means information that may be used to identify a specific individual, or that is about an identifiable individual, such as name, e-mail address or phone number.INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE ITYou can visit our sites and discover our products, services, companies and worldwide activities without providing personal information. To send further requests, use some of our services or receive newsletters, you will need to provide certain personal information. ANDRITZ does not collect any personal information unless you provide it voluntarily. You may also choose to provide personal information to us when visiting ANDRITZ locations or corresponding with us by mail or e-mail.Request/subscription forms:We may ask you to provide personal information in order to allow us to respond to your requests for information or other requests made over our website. As part of our request forms, we note your name, e-mail address, mailing address, other contact information (company, position in company, address, phone number) and data about your company. We may ask for other information in connection with specific products, services, events or other activities to better customize your website experience or our offers to you. We indicate at the time of data collection which information is mandatory and which is optional.E-Mail newsletter:On the newsletter section of the sites, you may provide us with your name and e-mail address in order to subscribe to different ANDRITZ newsletters that contain information about ANDRITZ and its activities. Alternatively, you may provide us with your mailing address in order to receive newsletters by mail.Subscription to events/services (Marketing Automation):On specific pages, you may provide us with your name, e-mail address and other business related data in order to obtain access to special services (e.g. whitepapers, webinars, consultation, proposals, events, etc.) and subscribe to different ANDRITZ e-mailings containing information about ANDRITZ and its activities.Mobile apps:When using third-party or ANDRITZ owned apps – which you download to your mobile device(s) voluntarily - you may provide us with your name, e-mail address and other business-related data in order to gain access to special services (e.g. e-magazines, whitepapers, webinars, consultation, events, etc.) and subscribe to different ANDRITZ newsletters containing information about ANDRITZ and its activities. These apps include analysis services as explained below.Customer magazines, communications:On subscription pages, you may provide us with your name, e-mail address, mailing address and other contact information (company, position in company, address, phone number) in order to subscribe to different ANDRITZ communication activities, which will be used to inform you about the ANDRITZ GROUP and its activities.Non-personal information:We collect non-personal information such as your Internet browser type, operating system, and the IP address of the website from which you are linked to the sites. We use this information to help us tailor our sites to better match your computer settings, interests and preferences.RETENTIONWe only process personal data for as long as necessary for the above-mentioned purposes. However, due to statutory retention requirements, we might also have to store personal data for a certain period of time even after these purposes have been achieved. Personal data required in order to be held harmless against any liability claims will be stored for as long as needed for this purpose.COOKIES POLICYANDRITZ wants to offer you the best online experience. Hence, we use cookies to analyze your website activity, internet and app usage, compile reports, optimize and personalize content and ads, as well as to provide social media features. We also share information about your usage of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.Cookies are small text files stored by your browser that allow us to learn more about your visit or use of the sites.Most browsers automatically accept cookies. To learn more about cookies, including how to refuse cookies on your computer, click here: https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/260971/description-of-cookiesANALYSIS SERVICESSeveral of the service providers that we use to analyze activities on our sites and our apps also offer opt-out mechanisms as an alternative to managing the placement of cookies by these services through your browser settings (see last chapter “Opt-out”).These analysis services provide the following information about the usage of our website and apps:Website activityInternet usageYour anonymized IP address (not associated with any other data)Only with your consent to our data privacy declaration through a double-opt-in process: your IP addressWe use this data to create a tailored web and app experience for you, to personalize our communication with you and to provide customized information, invitations and offers.OUR SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATIONANDRITZ does not sell or rent your personal information to non-affiliated third parties for those parties’ promotional purposes, except that as part of our customer care and marketing efforts, we may provide your name, address, contact details and similar information. In addition, ANDRITZ may share the personal information you submit with other members of our affiliated group of companies.Other than as described in the paragraphs above, ANDRITZ will not share your personal information with third parties without your permission, except as necessary or appropriate to (i) process or fulfill your order, (ii) respond to your requests or answer your inquiries, (iii) include you in promotional activities upon your request, (iv) comply with any applicable law, court order or other judicial process, or (v) enforce or apply agreements with you, or protect the rights, property or safety of ANDRITZ or third parties, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. In addition, in the event of a corporate transaction such as a sale, merger or reorganization involving ANDRITZ or its parent companies, personal information may be disclosed or transferred to the acquiring company(ies). ANDRITZ may collect and share aggregate website statistical information (such as sales, traffic patterns or related information) with third parties. No such shared statistics will contain any personally identifying user information.ANDRITZ may occasionally hire contractors to provide certain services on its behalf, including information processing and storage or the management of communication, marketing, promotional activities and surveys. These contractors are required to maintain the confidentiality of information they receive from ANDRITZ and are restricted from using the information for any purposes other than those authorized by ANDRITZ.Personal data will generally not be transmitted to recipients outside the European Union or the European Economic Area, unless it is required to fulfill the above-mentioned purposes. In these cases, we will ensure that such recipients are bound by respective data protection statutes (e.g. EU-US data privacy shield, standard contractual clauses).HOW ANDRITZ PROTECTS YOUR INFORMATIONWhen you submit any information via our sites, that information is subject to secure sockets layer (SSL) encryption technology. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information during transmission, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. Any personal information submitted to ANDRITZ in writing is kept in a secure location. Our instructions to our employees and computer service providers with access to your personal information state that they must comply with the principles set forth in this data privacy declaration and applicable laws.SUBMISSIONSSuggestions, materials or other intellectual property sent or transmitted to ANDRITZ via our sites or otherwise are governed by the separate terms applicable to such materials identified at the time of submission (if any). If no such terms are identified, all such items shall be deemed to be non-confidential and public domain, and ANDRITZ shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such items and shall be free to use and distribute them to others without limitation, including, but not limited to developing and marketing products incorporating them.CONTACT USIf you have any questions or comments about this data privacy declaration or your personal information, you may contact us by sending an e-mail to dataprotection@andritz.com, or by mail to ANDRITZ AG, Stattegger Strasse 18, 8045 Graz, Austria.Austrian data protection authorityIf you believe that your personal data has not been processed in accordance with the applicable laws, you can file a complaint with the Austrian data protection authority (“Datenschutzbehörde”) www.dsb.gv.at.YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR DATA PRIVACY DECLARATIONBy using our sites, or by submitting personal information, you signify your acceptance of this data privacy declaration, consent to our use of the personal information you submit to ANDRITZ in accordance with this data privacy declaration, and you agree to adhere to the terms and conditions posted on the sites under “Terms of use”. If you do not agree with the terms of this data privacy declaration, please do not submit any personal information to us.CHANGES TO THE DATA PRIVACY DECLARATIONANDRITZ reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so you should review it frequently. If we make changes to this privacy policy, we will post such changes here and/or on our sites.Effective date: May 25th, 2018Last updated on: January 15th, 2020Copyright © 2018 ANDRITZ AGOPT-OUTIf you wish to opt out of any of the data sharing practices described in this data privacy declaration, please use the following “Data subject request form”You may set your browser to reject cookies or to notify you when a web site tries to place cookies in your browser program. For your convenience, additional information about how to manage cookies for major browsers is available at the following links: Safari: LinkFirefox: LinkInternet Explorer: LinkChrome: Link
Go to data subject request form
By using the following web form, you can make use of your "data subject rights" and submit a request to an ANDRITZ company.These rights cover information about the personal data stored and processed by a company, the right to have one's personal data corrected, deleted or no longer processed (or only with certain restrictions), as well as the right to receive one's personal data in electronic form.
